<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Posture Reminder</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_causes">CausesActivity</string>


    <string name="causesTab_title1">Use of technology</string>
    <string name="causesTab_title2">Injury</string>
    <string name="causesTab_title3">Poor footwear</string>
    <string name="causesTab_title4">Stress and anxiety</string>
    <string name="causesTab_title5">Muscle weakness</string>


    <string name="causesTab_text1">If you text on your phone often, you may develop “text neck” — a condition caused by flexing your neck forward too often.  If you sit on the couch watching television for many hours each day, you may develop stooped shoulders and lower back problems. If you often sit in a chair without ergonomic support, your posture may eventually worsen. </string>
    <string name="causesTab_text2">If you have suffered from an injury, some of the muscles around the injury site may spasm to protect the part of your body that is vulnerable.  This is a normal physiological response designed to keep the injured part of your body stable.Unfortunately, the muscles that are spasming frequently can eventually weaken, which results in a muscular imbalance that may affect your posture.</string>
    <string name="causesTab_text3">If you wear shoes that are poorly fitted, your gait may be adversely affected.  It may cause you to walk in an unusual way, placing undue strain on your ankles, hips, or knees. This can eventually lead to poor posture.</string>
    <string name="causesTab_text4">Researchers have discovered that being in a stressed or anxious state can change how a person uses their body.  Stressed and anxious people tend to take shallower breaths and have more contracted muscles.  Unfortunately this can lead to poor posture.</string>
    <string name="causesTab_text5">If you have certain muscles that are much stronger or much weaker than others, it can encourage poor posture.  For example, if your abdominal muscles are weak from an insufficient amount of exercise, you may come to rely on back muscles for stability, leading to back pain. The solution to this common problem is a robust exercise regime that works out all of the major muscle groups. </string>


</resources>